Guide to the Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation: files of Steve Allen, photographer M1038
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- TGB447, TGB315, THJ320, THJ420 for Harlen Lawler 1/78 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- F6800 packages for Tom McGuire's distributor thing 12/20/78 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- 16K packages for dist. ad 9/78 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Package shot for cover of High Current VR book 8/2/78 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Package shot for cover of LIC Cons. Data Book 8/2/78 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- 96LS02 pkg photos for Judith Spelman and dist. ad 7/78 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Cupertino BBQ, for Francine Plaza 10/9/87 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- 1986 Facilities & MFG Scenes (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Applications slides, shot at Cupertino; MODEM, telephone trouble computer, Bruce Hildebr. 2/86 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Photos for Bruce Rainwater visit to Marelli, Italy 4/83 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- 4" wafer of the Exetron 6003 LCD, 5 function watch chip for Les Hogan 12/76 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- F16456 press release photo for Debbie Caldarulo, uP Div. 3/83 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Reliability Brochure II (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Reliability Brochure III slides (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Smithsonian Air Museum transparency copy neg for Lyn 11/76 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- FGC6000 plot CE1305 11/21/86 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Clasic photos for Corp. Legal (Steve Phillips) Sheri Sun 7/21/86 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Coolfet Copywrite photos for Helene Senkowski 8/18/86 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- More gate Array plots for Vivek Kulcarni 12/2/86 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- DELTA packaging,, Bill Phy R&D 1/86 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- 1986 Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Lead frame drawings for press releases, Jami Radow 7/15/87 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Power & Discretes catalog, photos with Suzy Lujan, Bookmake 6/87 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- H687/6687 PR photos 5/2/86 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- uA685 PR photo for Bill Orrange 4/7/86 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- More gate arrays pkgs for Lany Ross slide pitch, per Mike Adams 5/28/86 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Gate array pkgs with and w/o heat sinks for Michael Adams 5/6/86 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- 93Z667 PR photo 7/25/86 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- SOT23 PR photos 7/8/86 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- FAIRFACTS photos for Lise DiMartino 2/87 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Benson 3036 plotter for Mark MacGillivray 10/1/87 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- CTP NCIP Plotter for Mark Macgillivray, Benson 9/1/87 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Benson plotter for Mark MacGillivray 6/87 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- TO-220 lead former machine instruction manual photos for Don Lapray, Chuck Moberg 6/76 (Box 28, Folder 51)
- Gate array plots for Vivek Kulkarni's visit to Fujitsu 11/7/86 (Box 28, Folder 52)
- Additional photos for hybrid brochure-catalog 6/76 (Box 28, Folder 53)
- FNA 0006 for PROGRESS 6/77 (Box 28, Folder 54)
- Micropak 10/2 (Box 28, Folder 55)
- EPI. chips w/ comparisons-salt. paper clip and IBM car... (Box 28, Folder 56)
- Wild pix Micrologic devices and Tom Luke (Box 28, Folder 57)
- EMB Wafer (Box 28, Folder 58)
- Micrologic Devices in Instrumentation 7100 (Box 28, Folder 59)
- Good close-ups, Micrologics (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Xincom quad tester for quarterly report cover 7/77 (Box 28, Folder 61)
- Misc. slides 6/84 (Box 28, Folder 62)
- Horizons 3/86 (Box 28, Folder 63)
- GTO 750 pkg, socket thing for Bryan McMahon 2/82 (Box 28, Folder 64)
- 132 pin pkg for gate arrays Robert Nalesnik 6/82 (Box 28, Folder 65)
- Helping Hand project for Gray Allen 12/87 (Box 28, Folder 66)
- Hybrid display box for Rodney Smith 3/76 (Box 28, Folder 67)
- Ford ignition module proposal photos for Rodney Smith 5/76 (Box 28, Folder 68)
- Photos for mockup of E-100 box for Rodney Smith, Pete Kunedt 4/76 (Box 28, Folder 69)
- TO-3 regulator package for Bill Silver & Bill Callaham 8/76 (Box 28, Folder 70)
- Negs of Jerry Nalwajko's Display boards showing Mem. chip comparisons 8/77 (Box 28, Folder 71)
- Slides showing 16K IL wafer and CCD area imaging wafer for Les Hogan talk 6/77 (Box 28, Folder 72)
- 9762 whole wafer photo for Joan Bottero 4/77 (Box 28, Folder 73)
- Extra slide dupes for Les Hogan 3/77 (Box 28, Folder 74)
- LED panel displays 1978? (Box 28, Folder 75)
- Auto module display board for Rodney Smith, by Ed Garrigues 9/78 (Box 28, Folder 76)
- Voltage regulator display board photos for Larry Wittenbaugh 11/78 (Box 28, Folder 77)
- Hybrid analog mem. radio suitcase kit think (Voxson) for Jerry Markus 1/78 (Box 28, Folder 78)
- Walter Borlase 10/6/86 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Dan Garza 6/86 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Steve Jordan 5/9/86 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Phillipe Cornet for Momentum 11/12/86 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Francine Grace Plaza 10/17/86 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Latest hybrid display board 9/11/78 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Zener diodes for dist. ad 9/78 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Package layout for Bill Matlack and Future Elect 2/78 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Gate array pkgs for Hively 5/78 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- New-Hire orientation slides for Barbara Lapoint 9/78 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- CCs basketball photos 3/8/86 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Solid State Amp. MS 160 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- BLASE boards for Dan Wilnai 6/78 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Flame 16 board 6/29/78 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Puyallup chemical handling equipment for Horizons; negs by someone at Puyallup 6/85 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- "Thermostat" alone and with Spark 16 for Dan Wilnai 12/19/78 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Slides for Rodney Smith's trip showing hybrid products and production areas 1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Slides of MOS equip. in S. SJ plant for Dave Marriott with Dan Barbato 1/24/77 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- PEP 387x with "customer" test board for Herb Brunner 12/20/78 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- VW ignition module as installed in VW bus for Jim Holt 3/78 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Eric Breeze's photos of his dual picture TV stuff 4/78 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Dupes and internegs from Jon Brenneis, Annual Report pix 5/78 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Schlumberger facilities 1987 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- More slides from the hybrid brochure 1976 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Power Transistor brochure photos 4/76 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Benson CTP NCIP plotter photos for Bob Hines 10/86 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- John DeHaven, Benson employee of the month #4 7/87 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Benson exteriors, for Mark MacGillivray, flash reflection 6/19/87 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Bensons staff portraits for Teresa Leyerle 5/87 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Dennis Stuckey-Kauffman Benson employee of the month for Donna Pombo 6/87 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Benson. exteriors for Marie Headley 2/87 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Benson R&D lab for Mark MacGillivray 6/19/87 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Benson plots, for Mark MacGillivray 6/87 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- PEP 45 board 7/1/82 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Gate Array pkgs and CAD slides for Robert Nalesnik 8/16/82 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Timeband clock for Teddi Kush 12/77 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- New shot of uP demo board for PROGRESS 12/77 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- More F-8 Boards from Larry Choice for Van Lewing's European sesminars 10/77 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Memory board 95000130 for Patti Greig's data sheet 8/19/77 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Dupes from Garrigues slide showing Fairchild clocks on full background 9/77 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Migent Modem for Dave Barnes, Francine Plaza 6/87 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Coupler package from an airbrushed, dropout masked print (Original photo in 1977 file) 3/78 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- More pix of FSC Dolby board in Pioneer tape rec., car radio, AM FM portable; for Taira, Benedi.. 7/76 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Horizons 6,7/86 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Singapore, copy neg from Bill Callahan's slide 1/77 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- LIC Hi Rel for Larry Wittenbaugh's capabilities brochure 1/84 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Sign and front of Bldg 20 slides for John Salazar and KQED 10/83 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- Toxic spill exercise at San Rafael for Francine Plaza 10/84 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Hybrid Products Div. Bldg. 19 4/16/83 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- So. Portland plant for Don Brooks video 5/85 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- FAST devices for magazine 10/78 (Box 29, Folder 52)
- FSC Dolby board with Pioneer tape deck Dolby circuit for Gary Pumphrey, sid Bagwe 5/76 (Box 29, Folder 53)
- FSC corporate hdgs, Cupertino, Calif. 4/8/86 (Box 29, Folder 54)
- Photo of lenses for line scan COD camera data sheet 9/76 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- New batch of Timeband watches from John Hatch 12/6/77 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Auto clock, Technology kit 3/77 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Two new ladies LCD watches for John Hatch's European show 4/77 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Custom F-8 PC board for Litton microwave oven 1/77 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- CCD321M demonstration board 1/77 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- LED Digital bathroom scale retouched photo from '77 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous photographs, and negatives (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Automation slides for Mark Schnieder, Geog Kuhnke 11/83 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- BXB 0212 open pkgs for Brent Knudson 9/76 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- TO-5 and plastic Mini DIP packages for FuAF356TC/7629 8/76 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- TBA820L packages photo for Bill Callahan 8/76 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Power transistor packages for Howard Bogrow 6/76 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- MSI vs. Macrologic package comparison for John East, AMD 2900 and FSC 9405 5/76 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- 6E package photos for Joe Murphy 2/76 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Fairfacts photos 4/86 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- 1986 IR, PR, & collateral (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Misc. slides from Don Brooks Video 5/85 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- MOS packaging slides for Walt Noll 2/76 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Package press release photos for Bill Callahan 10/76 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Macrologic package for Geri's Ogilvy-Mather macrologic ad 9/76 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Hybrid packages for the Hybrid Data Book 5/78 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Delco module, Kodachrome slides for Frank Bower 5/78 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Kent Dahlgren, uContr. PME? 1/86 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Satellite and rocket slides from NASA transparencies for Jim Townsend 7/74 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- 2nd Q 1987 photos for Francine Plaza (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Beam tape lead pkg for Bob Trabucco 5/11/82 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- uA565 press release photo for Bob Frostholm (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Don Brooks, Peyton Cole candids for Janis Ulevich 4/4/85 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Ed Fernandez mktg group 10/7/87 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- John Yamanaka passport 10/14/87 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Corp. strategic mktg. staff plus 10/3/87 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Surindar Krishna and Kulwant Egan, authors of CLASIC mag. art. for Jami Radow 3/12/87 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Kamal Aggarwal, Analog Div Mgr; for Momentum 4/14/87 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Fred Brinkmann 3/87 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- SL30994 package photos for Rich Hansen and Hughs 5/76 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- CCD area imager with fiber optic lid for Rudy Dyck 3/83 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Gate Array photos for Schlumberger guarterly 9/84 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Package shots for Ellen Hipscham, LIC 10/19/83 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Spark 16, latest version 8/25/78 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- CLASIC slides for Tom Wei 8/86 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- "CLASSIC" pkgs, for Steve Kaufman 2/86 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- 9451 and 52 pkgs, for Kent Porter and Karron Esme 3/13/86 (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Gate array pkg types, for Nanci Magoun 1/15/86 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- uController packages R&D shot, for Martin Plotkin 1986 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Recruiting brochure 'chromes for Lise DeMartino; from me and various other sources 6/86 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- SOIC pkgs Dig. Div., for Janis Ulevice press release 2/3/86 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- More wafer fab and HiRel assembly slides for Warren Johnson and Martin Reed 4/83 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Industrial Prod. and another div. building dupe slides 1978? (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Aerial view of FSC MV complex, copy neg from blurry print 6/78 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- Slide showing plant and xx sales locations for new-hire slide program-Barbara Lapoint 10/5/78 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- PLL board for Eric Breeze 9/28/78 (Box 30, Folder 52)
- Breadboard of uA7743, variable speech control, for Doug Simin 5/78 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- Timeband chronograph watch 3/15/78 (Box 30, Folder 54)
- ALIC fab, Bldg 2 Analog; for Jim Holt 2/28/86 (Box 30, Folder 55)
- Electron beam machine in the mask making shop 8/77 (Box 30, Folder 56)
- Slides of Bernal Rd. plant interior for MOS CCD slide talk at sales conf. for Geo. Urbani 1/78 (Box 30, Folder 57)
- Micro Systems boards etc. at Systems for Dean Bennett, for Product Liner 4/78 (Box 30, Folder 58)
- Fire project photos and slides 1/78 (Box 30, Folder 59)
- OCM-1 board with 3870 modification for Dean Bennett 5/78 (Box 30, Folder 60)
- OCM-1 board microprocessor 5/24/78 (Box 30, Folder 61)
- 1x2 Hybrid pkg for Jim Holt 7/77 (Box 30, Folder 62)
- 8 chip, #2004 hybrid for Tom Courtney, Jurii Klonizchii 1/77 (Box 30, Folder 63)
- Voxson module in front of Pinto radio; Helen Smith's finger 6/77 (Box 30, Folder 64)
- Voxson panel photo for Jerry Markus 7/21/77 (Box 30, Folder 65)
- Ignition module for Jerry Markus 5/77 (Box 30, Folder 66)